<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Lagos</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="music_fragment">Music</string>
    <string name="parks_fragment">Parks</string>
    <string name="monuments_fragment">Monuments</string>
    <string name="restaurants_fragment">Restaurants</string>
    <string name="image_of_the_attraction">Image of the Attraction</string>
    <string name="info1">MUSON Centre, (Musical Society of Nigeria) is a performance hall in Lagos. \n\n The multipurpose civic auditorium is located in the heart of Lagos Island, situated conspicuously between the National Museum, the City Mall, the Onikan Stadium and the former official residence of the Nigeria’s Governors-Generals and adjacent to Tafawa Balewa Square. \n\n Type: Performing-arts center \n\n Established: 1983</string>
    <string name="muson_center">Muson Center</string>
    <string name="title_activity_afrika_shrine">AfrikaShrineActivity</string>
    <string name="info_shrine">The New Afrika Shrine is an open air entertainment centre located in Ikeja, Lagos State. It serves as the host location of the annual Felabration music festival. \n\nCurrently managed by Femi Kuti and Yeni Anikulapo-Kuti, it is the replacement of the old Afrika Shrine created in 1970 by Fela Kuti until it was burnt down in 1977. \n\nThe New Afrika Shrine showcases photo galleries of Fela and music performances by Femi Kuti and Seun Kuti thus making it a tourist attraction. \n\n</string>
    <string name="info_bay_lounge">Bay Lounge is a new destination restaurant and lounge tucked in the swanky Lekki neighborhood in Lagos. \n\nBay Lounge is committed to serving you with great food using only the best ingredients. Our extensive menu includes lip smacking local and international dishes with the option to dine ‘al fresco’. Tempting salads, signature club sandwich mouth watering seafood are just a few of our freshly made food. \n\nPhone: 0809 999 9827 \n\n</string>
    <string name="info_calabar">Calabar Kitchen is a full-service café/restaurant located in the District of Lagos. The restaurant features a full menu of moderately priced “comfort” food featuring delicious, mouth watering, well prepared African and Continental delicacies based upon time honored recipes in a serene environment. \n\nCalabar Kitchen is a name to beat when it comes to African food, and this is what we bring to the satisfaction of our guests. \n\nContact : +2348033665979 \n\n</string>
    <string name="info_ekaabo">The dining room at Ekaabo Restaurant is well apportioned with optimum use of the space. The layout was tastefully done with gorgeous white skylights suspended from the high ceilings. \n\nThey also had the imposing champagne wall at the bar like they had at Milano Restaurant. The most outstanding piece of the décor here is the fountain out on the terrace.\n\nPhone: 01 236 6666 \n\n</string>
    <string name="info_freedom_park">Freedom Park is a memorial and leisure park area in the middle of downtown Lagos in Lagos Island, Nigeria. \n\nThe Park was constructed to preserve the history and cultural heritage of Nigerians. Monuments in the park reveal the Lagos colonial heritage and history of Her Majesty\'s Broad Street prisons. \n\nIt was built to commemorate the 50th anniversary independence celebration in October, 2010. The Park serves as a National Memorial, a Historical landmark, a Cultural site, Arts and Recreation centre. \n\n The park, which is now a serene abode for individuals, visitors\' collective contemplation and interaction is open to the public every day. Today, freedom park has become a venue for diverse social events and recreational entertainment.</string>
    <string name="info_fun_factory">FUNFACTORY is a recreational and entertainment park for kids. \n\nFunfactory facilities include toys, games, bouncy castles, train rides, carousels, swimming pools and so many other creative and interactive games for children between the ages of 1 to 10. \n\nFunfactory is neatly laid out on over 3000 sq metres of colourful Astroturf grass, providing ambience, safety and excitement at the same time. \n\n</string>
    <string name="info_jazzhole">Mr Tejuoso founded Jazzhole as an offshoot of Glendora, the legendary bookstore franchise founded by his mother. \n\nHe started it in a time when a lot of expatriates were resident in Lagos and he wanted to provide them with a place to get international music here in Lagos. \n\nJazzhole has become much more than a collector or music retailer, he’s become a historian of African culture, fighting to preserve it for the coming generation through its music. \n\n</string>
    <string name="info_kilimanjaro">Kilimanjaro is one of Sundry Foods’ restaurant brands, operating in the Quick Service Restaurant (QSR) segment, the brand has established itself as a market leader and one of the fastest growing restaurant brands in the country with currently 24 stores across Nigeria and more to come. \n\nKilimanjaro caters to the unique preference of the general populace in this part of sub-saharan Africa for their local dishes. Our unique menu consists of select popular contemporary and Nigerian offerings. \n\nOur popular meals include: Plantain Porridge and Beef Kebab, Yam Fritters and Breaded Fish, Okro Soup and swallow, etc. \n\n</string>
    <string name="info_lcc">From its origin and establishment in 1990 by the Nigerian Conservation Foundation (NCF), Lekki Conservation Centre (LCC) has grown into one of Africa’s prominent and most-diverse urban Nature Parks due to its high species richness. \n\nLekki Conservation Centre represents the flagship project of NCF for the preservation of the unique biodiversity, scenic, natural, scientific and recreational values of the coastal environs of the south-western Nigeria. \n\nIt is therefore one of the best urban parks to satiate visitors’ curiosity of nature. \n\n</string>
    <string name="info_lll">Lekki Leisure Lake is a lake side resort overlooking the Atlantic in the Lekki peninsula area. The resort is operated and managed by Optima Leisure, a leisure and hospitality company based in Lagos. \n\nLekki Leisure Lake offers the thrill of jet skiing in a safe environment, under the watchful eye and guidance of an instructor. \n\n</string>
    <string name="info_museum">Established in 1957, National Museum Lagos has great collections in archaeology, ethnography and traditional art. National Museum displays contemporary arts and historical monuments. \n\nThe main attractions at the museum are the galleries dedicated to brasses from Benin City, Nok Terracottas etc. \n\nAnother gallery dedicated to traditional symbols of power contains carved ivory and a royal host of crowns. The museum houses the bullet-riddled car in which the country’s former Head of State – late General Murtala Mohammed – was assassinated in 1976. \n\nIt opens daily (except Sundays) from 9am to 5pm. \n\n</string>
    <string name="info_stadium">The Lagos National Stadium is a multi-purpose stadium which comprises an Olympic-size swimming arena and a multipurpose arena used for basketball, volleyball, table tennis, wrestling and boxing matches. \n\nIt was used mostly for football matches until 2001. It hosted several international competitions including the 1980 African Cup of Nations final, the 2000 African Cup of Nations final, and FIFA World Cup qualifying matches. \n\nIt also served as the main stadium for the 1973 All-Africa Games. When the stadium was built in 1972, it had a capacity of 55,000. The capacity was then reduced to 45,000 in 1999. \n\nThe record attendance is 85,000 and was taken in the final match of the African Cup of Nations in 1980 between Nigeria and Algeria.</string>
    <string name="info_theatre">The National Arts Theatre is the primary centre for the performing arts in Nigeria. Construction was completed in 1976 in preparation for the Festival of Arts and Culture (FESTAC) in 1977. \n\nThe National Arts Theatre was built during the military regime of Olusegun Obasanjo. The collection of National Gallery of Modern Nigerian Art is housed in a section of this building. \n\nIts exterior is shaped like a military hat. It has a 5,000-seater Main Hall with a collapsible stage, and two capacity cinema halls. \n\n</string>
    <string name="info_tarkwa_bay">Tarkwa Bay is an artificial sheltered beach located near the Lagos harbour. \n\nDue to its island status, it is only accessible by boat or water taxis. \n\nThe beach, popular with swimmers and water-sports enthusiasts, also has a welcoming resident community. \n\n</string>
    <string name="info_tbs">The Tafawa Balewa Square, (TBS) is a 14.5-hectare (35.8-acre) ceremonial ground (originally called “Race Course”). \n\nTBS was constructed in 1972 over the site of a defunct rack for horse racing. It is bounded by Awolowo road, Cable Street, Force road, Catholic Mission street and the 26-storey independence building. \n\nThe entrance to the square has gigantic sculptures of four white horses hovering above the gate and seven red eagles, which are symbols from the national emblem signifying Strength and Dignity respectively. \n\nThe square has a capacity for 50,000 people. Facilities at the square include a shopping center, Airline\'s Travel Agencies, restaurants and car parking and a bus terminal. \nMajor national events at TBS includes Nigeria’s independence celebration which took place on October 1, 1960 with the Prime Minister, Tafawa Balewa, delivering his speech. Democracy Day, as well as other multifarious events such as musical jamborees and religious gatherings.</string>
    <string name="info_terrakulture">Terra Kulture is an arts and culture center in Lagos with an attached restaurant. \n\nNigerian lawyer Bolanle Austen-Peters founded Terra Kulture in 2003. \n\nAnnual events at Terra Kulture includes an art auction[7] and the Taruwa festival of Performing arts. \n\n</string>
    <string name="info_tmb">The Third Mainland Bridge is the longest of three bridges connecting Lagos Island to the mainland, the other two being the Eko and Carter bridges. \n\nIt was the longest bridge in Africa until 1996 when the 6th October Bridge located in Cairo was completed. \n\nThe bridge was built by Julius Berger Nigeria PLC and opened by President Ibrahim Babangida in 1990. \n\nIt measures about 11.8 km in length.</string>
    <string name="kilimanjaro">Kilimanjaro</string>
    <string name="calabar_kitchen">Calabar Kitchen</string>
    <string name="bay_lounge">Bay Lounge</string>
    <string name="ekaabo">Ekaabo</string>
    <string name="national_stadium">National Stadium</string>
    <string name="national_theatre">National Theatre</string>
    <string name="tbs">Tafawa Balewa Square</string>
    <string name="tmb">Third Mainland Bridge</string>
    <string name="museum">National Museum</string>
    <string name="fun_factory">Fun Factory</string>
    <string name="tarkwa_bay">Tarkwa Bay</string>
    <string name="lll">Lekki Leisure Lake</string>
    <string name="lcc">Lekki Conservation Center</string>
    <string name="afrika_shrine">Afrika Shrine</string>
    <string name="jazzhole">Jazzhole</string>
    <string name="terrakulture">Terra Kulture</string>
    <string name="freedom_park">Freedom Park</string>
</resources>
